var data = [
  {
    "category": "IT 101",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What Zendesk status do you use when you are waiting for a response from a user?",
        "answer": "Pending"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "What approval(s) is required for secondary devices?",
        "answer": "Supervisor & IT (Krystal/Clarissa)"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "A Windows user is unable to add a printer using PrinterLogic even though they are clicking install. What do they do?",
        "answer": "Refresh Configurations/End PrinterLogicInterface.exe tasks"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "A user is saying that their account is deactivated. What do you do first?",
        "answer": "Check the tickets"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "MBM/PBM",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What is the guiding principle that starts with the letter 'P'?",
        "answer": "Principled Entrepreneurship"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "Is sharing your knowledge a part of a guiding principle? Which one? ",
        "answer": "Yes, Knowledge"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "How many Principles of Human Progress are there? What are they called?",
        "answer": "5: Dignity, Openness, Bottom Up, Mutual Benefit. Self-Actualize"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What are the five dimensions of the MBM framework?",
        "answer": "Vision, Virtue & Talents, Knowledge Process, Decision Rights, Incentives"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "The Office",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "Where can you find headsets in our IT Space?",
        "answer": "The rightmost closet out of the 4 closets with the 1310 door code"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "I am a cold drink that everbody wants in the morning, where am I in the office?",
        "answer": "Cold Brew - 2nd Floor"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What are two soft drinks that can be found in 1310 but not in 1320?",
        "answer": "Dr.Pepper & Mtn Dew"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What's the room number for the server room that keeps beeping all the time?",
        "answer": "410"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Feeling Lucky",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What is Earth's largest continent?",
        "answer": "Asia"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "Which of Newton's Laws states that for every action, there is an equal and opposite reaction?",
        "answer": "The third law of motion"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "Which is the only edible food that never goes bad?",
        "answer": "Honey"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "How many hearts does an octapus have?",
        "answer": "3"
      }
    ]
  }
];